(Amy:)That is a cleverly veiled reference
to Howard's lifelong obsession...
(Amy:)...to crawl back into her spacious womb.
(Penny:)Anyway, to this day, I still can't see a box
of crayons without crossing my legs. Ha, ha.
(Bernadette:)I don't have to take this.
(Bernadette:)I'm gonna go home
and have sex with my husband right now.
(Bernadette:)Maybe I'll let him do it to me
in the parking spot.
(Bernadette:)Which sounds dirty
but I didn't mean it that way.
Okay, here's another one.
If a zombie bites a vampire...
...and the vampire bites a human...
...does the human become a vampire
or a zombie?
Or a zompire?
(Leonard:)Sheldon?
Cookie?
- I don't have any.
- Well, I'm not giving it away.
- Hi, Sheldon.
- Aah!